x

Menu

Menu

JavaScript is disabled. For a better experience, please enable JavaScript in your browser before proceeding.

Help pages

Help
----

Privacy policy
==============

We are F95zone ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information, please [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/).

Privacy
-------

For your peace of mind, we would like to ensure that under no circumstances will your email or personal information be shared with or distributed to anyone without your explicit consent. Your privacy is extremely important to us. Please be mindful not to share your email publicly when posting, as the site allows user contributions and posts.

Joining only requires an email address, which serves as the only unique & reliable identifier for our users. We ask for no other identifiers. You are permitted to change your “display name” at any time; however, your login will always be your original registered email. There are no “name” fields, so you are not required or encouraged to use your real name, nor submit any other personal information, address, or phone number.

We do not know your password. It is stored in an encrypted hash. You may [reset your password anytime](https://f95zone.to/lost-password/), and we have recently removed the restriction of forcing very strong passwords when resetting. Once logged in, the account/settings page allows you to change your password.

Users may voluntarily enter their city (or country) on their profile card to let other users know where they are located – purely for interest's sake and no other reason. It is beneficial to know when someone is from another country, enabling us to translate our communications into their native language. We strongly encourage an international community, as we are multilingual ourselves.

Naturally, some basic and general information (such as browser type, device, and IP address, etc.) is occasionally logged along with any submissions for visitor & statistic purposes. These logs are essential for gaining a general understanding of our audience and assist in debugging, depending on the browser/device you’re using.

However, it’s important to note that in specific circumstances, particularly in compliance with our CSAM policy or when legally required, we may be obligated to provide certain information to authorities. We take our legal responsibilities seriously while striving to protect your privacy to the fullest extent possible.

Data Retention Policy
---------------------

We retain your personal information for a period of 50 days to provide you with our services. After this period, personal data is securely deleted from our systems unless we are obligated to retain it longer for legal reasons, particularly in relation to our CSAM policy. Our retention policy is designed to respect your privacy while ensuring we meet our legal and ethical responsibilities.

Children’s Privacy & CSAM
-------------------------

Our services are not directed to children under the age of 18. We take the protection of children's privacy very seriously and comply with all applicable laws and regulations on child protection. For detailed information on our stance and actions against Child Sexual Abuse Material (CSAM), please refer to our dedicated CSAM Policy at [F95Zone CSAM Policy](https://f95zone.to/help/csam/).

Forum Registration
------------------

Registration is necessary to participate and post in our forum. A registration form should be filled out completely with your desired username, password, and email address. Your email address will be used to verify your membership and contact you about forum-related concerns. We process and store the information collected on this website securely and in accordance with applicable privacy laws. We do not share any personally identifying information with outside third parties without your consent, except as required by law.

Forum User Information
----------------------

If you are a forum member, please be aware that when you share or post personally identifying information, that information can be seen, stored, or utilized by other forum members whom you choose to share the information with. This may result in you receiving unsolicited messages and other forms of communication, depending on the information you shared. F95zone.com will not be responsible for personally identifying information that you share or post in the forum.

Log Files
---------

Log files contain information that is usually made available by your web browser and is stored on our web server. This non-personally identifying information includes the following: browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of every page request. Just like most other sites, we collect this information to have a better understanding of how our visitors use our website, to be able to generate reports on the trends relevant to the usage of our website, help with website administration, analyze user activities on the site, and collect information about our user base in general. We do not link the information contained in these log files to personally identifying information, and we will never distribute them to outside third parties.

What Information We Collect
---------------------------

When using forums provided by F95zone.com, we may require some or all of the following information:

* email address
* Internet Protocol (IP) address
* geographical location
* browser type and version
* operating system
* referral source
* length of visit, page views, website navigation, and any other related browsing activity

Cookies and Web Beacons
-----------------------

A cookie is a small text file that a website stores on your computer. This file contains information that your browser provides to the website each time you return. Cookies are used for record-keeping purposes. A web beacon is a transparent graphical image that serves to monitor your interaction with a website. This, along with cookies and log files, provides us with analytical information that we can use to improve website performance and user experience in general. We do not link this information to personally identifying information, nor do we give this information to outside third parties. This privacy statement regarding the use of cookies and web beacons is only applicable to the F95zone.com website.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on [this page](https://f95zone.to/help/cookies).

Third Party Ads
---------------

Our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons in the ads that they serve on our website. The use of such technologies will enable the advertiser to store information about your web surfing interests, so that they can show you targeted advertisements that they believe will interest you the most. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and web beacons in the ads of our third-party advertisers.

Managing Cookies
----------------

If you do not wish to enable cookies, simply adjust your browser settings before using our website and turn off cookies for F95zone.com or our third-party advertisers. Bear in mind, however, that disabling cookies may affect how our site will function for you (e.g., being unable to log in).

Links to Other Sites
--------------------

Our website contains links leading to other websites that are not owned or managed by us. Because we are not responsible for how these sites handle your privacy, we encourage you to check out the Privacy Policies of those other websites before giving out your personal information.

Keeping Your Data Secure
------------------------

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

Controlling Your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

When using the F95zone.com forum, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account.

F95zone.com will not sell, distribute, or lease your personal information to third parties. We may use your personal information to send you security information, updates, or other information pertaining to F95zone.com, or your account.

Rights
------

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so, please [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/). If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/) to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please [contact us](https://f95zone.to/pages/contact/) if you would like us to remove your personal data.

Acceptance of This Policy
-------------------------

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy, then please do not use this site. When registering, we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

Changes to This Policy
----------------------

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.

**Last updated:** April 22, 2024

### About us

F95zone is an adult community where you can find tons of great adult games and comics, make new friends, participate in active discussions and more!

### Quick Navigation

### User Menu

### Forum statistics

Threads

214,422

Messages

14,175,409

Members

7,928,860

Latest member

This site provides links to other sites/services, and does not store any files

* 
* [UI.X Dark \[Old and unsupported\]](https://f95zone.to/misc/style "Style chooser")

Served by: \[NUMA||US\]-\[S2|10.39/10.12/10.41\] \[192e41d13d3\] (d24ff2f3)
